https://www.thecleverbaggers.co.uk/privacy-policy

+44 (0)1938 530 050
Basket
(0)
Christmas
Party Goody Bags Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Tote Gift Bags Bottle Gift Bags Christmas Stockings Drawstring Sacks Christmas Fabric Craft Packaging for Post
Tote Bags
Style
Hand Tote Bags Shoulder Tote Bags Cross Body Tote Bags Party Goody Tote Bags Shopper Tote Bags Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Tote Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Natural Jute Tote Bags Natural Hemp Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Coloured Jute Tote Bags
Material
Jute Tote Bags Jute+Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Tote Bags Hemp Cotton Tote Bags
Best Seller Tote Bags Sale Tote Bags
Drawstring Bags
Style
Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Storage Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Drawstring Bottle Bags Drawstring Party Goody Bags Drawstring Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Drawstring Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Natural Jute Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Coloured Voile Drawstring Bags
Material
Jute Drawstring Bags Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Cotton Drawstring Bags Voile Drawstring Bags
Best Seller Drawstring Bags Sale Drawstring Bags
Aprons
Style
Full Bib Aprons Waist Aprons
Colour
White Polycotton Aprons Coloured Polycotton Aprons Coloured Cotton Aprons Natural Linen Aprons
Material
Polycotton Aprons Cotton Aprons Linen Aprons
Sale Aprons
Zip Pouches
Style
Pencil/Make up Cases Tablet Cases
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Coloured Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Natural Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Material
Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Sale Zip Pouches
Tea Towels
Colour
White Cotton Tea Towels White Linen Tea Towels White Linen Cotton Tea Towels Natural Linen Tea Towels Coloured Cotton Tea Towels
Material
Cotton Tea Towels Linen Tea Towels Linen Cotton Tea Towels
Budget Tea Towels Sale Tea Towels
Fabric Craft
Fabric Paint Iron on Images Fabric Pens & Crayons Iron on Craft Transfer Paper Wooden Stamps Christmas Stockings Sale Fabric Craft
Home Textiles
Product
Cushion Covers Cushion Pads Table Napkins Table Runners Table Mats Christmas Stockings
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers White Cotton Tableware White Linen Cotton Tableware Coloured Cotton Cushion Covers Coloured Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Natural Cotton Christmas Stockings Natural Jute Christmas Stockings Coloured Cotton Christmas Stockings
Material
Cotton Cushion Covers Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Cotton Christmas Stockings Jute Christmas Stockings
Tableware Budget Table Napkins Sale Home Textiles
Hygiene Wear
Face Coverings Aprons Laundry Bags Hygiene Wear Storage
Packaging
Drawstring Packaging Bags Paper Packaging
Sale
Sale Tote Bags Sale Drawstring Bags Sale Aprons Sale Tea Towels Sale Home Textiles
+44 (0)1938 530 050
Basket
(0)
/ £0.00
You have no items in your basket
Subtotal
£0.00
View Basket Checkout
Sign In
Search
X
Christmas
Party Goody Bags Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Tote Gift Bags Bottle Gift Bags Christmas Stockings Drawstring Sacks Christmas Fabric Craft Packaging for Post
Tote Bags
Style
Hand Tote Bags Shoulder Tote Bags Cross Body Tote Bags Party Goody Tote Bags Shopper Tote Bags Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Tote Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Natural Jute Tote Bags Natural Hemp Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Coloured Jute Tote Bags
Material
Jute Tote Bags Jute+Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Tote Bags Hemp Cotton Tote Bags
Best Seller Tote Bags Sale Tote Bags
Drawstring Bags
Style
Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Storage Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Drawstring Bottle Bags Drawstring Party Goody Bags Drawstring Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Drawstring Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Natural Jute Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Coloured Voile Drawstring Bags
Material
Jute Drawstring Bags Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Cotton Drawstring Bags Voile Drawstring Bags
Best Seller Drawstring Bags Sale Drawstring Bags
Aprons
Style
Full Bib Aprons Waist Aprons
Colour
White Polycotton Aprons Coloured Polycotton Aprons Coloured Cotton Aprons Natural Linen Aprons
Material
Polycotton Aprons Cotton Aprons Linen Aprons
Sale Aprons
Zip Pouches
Style
Pencil/Make up Cases Tablet Cases
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Coloured Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Natural Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Material
Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Sale Zip Pouches
Tea Towels
Colour
White Cotton Tea Towels White Linen Tea Towels White Linen Cotton Tea Towels Natural Linen Tea Towels Coloured Cotton Tea Towels
Material
Cotton Tea Towels Linen Tea Towels Linen Cotton Tea Towels
Budget Tea Towels Sale Tea Towels
Fabric Craft
Fabric Paint Iron on Images Fabric Pens & Crayons Iron on Craft Transfer Paper Wooden Stamps Christmas Stockings Sale Fabric Craft
Home Textiles
Product
Cushion Covers Cushion Pads Table Napkins Table Runners Table Mats Christmas Stockings
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers White Cotton Tableware White Linen Cotton Tableware Coloured Cotton Cushion Covers Coloured Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Natural Cotton Christmas Stockings Natural Jute Christmas Stockings Coloured Cotton Christmas Stockings
Material
Cotton Cushion Covers Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Cotton Christmas Stockings Jute Christmas Stockings
Tableware Budget Table Napkins Sale Home Textiles
Hygiene Wear
Face Coverings Aprons Laundry Bags Hygiene Wear Storage
Packaging
Drawstring Packaging Bags Paper Packaging
Sale
Sale Tote Bags Sale Drawstring Bags Sale Aprons Sale Tea Towels Sale Home Textiles
Search
X
+44 (0)1938 530 050
Basket
(0)
/ £0.00
You have no items in your basket
Subtotal
£0.00
View Basket Checkout
Sign In
Christmas
Party Goody Bags
Christmas
Party Goody Bags Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Tote Gift Bags Bottle Gift Bags Christmas Stockings Drawstring Sacks Christmas Fabric Craft Packaging for Post
Tote Bags
Style
Hand Tote Bags Shoulder Tote Bags Cross Body Tote Bags Party Goody Tote Bags Shopper Tote Bags Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Tote Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Natural Jute Tote Bags Natural Hemp Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Tote Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Coloured Jute Tote Bags
Material
Jute Tote Bags Jute+Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Canvas Tote Bags Cotton Tote Bags Hemp Cotton Tote Bags
Best Seller Tote Bags Sale Tote Bags
Drawstring Bags
Style
Drawstring Gift Bags Drawstring Storage Bags Drawstring Packaging Bags Drawstring Bottle Bags Drawstring Party Goody Bags Drawstring Sports Bags
Colour
Natural Cotton Drawstring Bags Natural Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Natural Jute Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Drawstring Bags Coloured Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Coloured Voile Drawstring Bags
Material
Jute Drawstring Bags Cotton Canvas Drawstring Bags Cotton Drawstring Bags Voile Drawstring Bags
Best Seller Drawstring Bags Sale Drawstring Bags
Aprons
Style
Full Bib Aprons Waist Aprons
Colour
White Polycotton Aprons Coloured Polycotton Aprons Coloured Cotton Aprons Natural Linen Aprons
Material
Polycotton Aprons Cotton Aprons Linen Aprons
Sale Aprons
Zip Pouches
Style
Pencil/Make up Cases Tablet Cases
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Coloured Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Natural Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Material
Cotton Canvas Zip Pouches Hemp Cotton Zip Pouches
Sale Zip Pouches
Tea Towels
Colour
White Cotton Tea Towels White Linen Tea Towels White Linen Cotton Tea Towels Natural Linen Tea Towels Coloured Cotton Tea Towels
Material
Cotton Tea Towels Linen Tea Towels Linen Cotton Tea Towels
Budget Tea Towels Sale Tea Towels
Fabric Craft
Fabric Paint Iron on Images Fabric Pens & Crayons Iron on Craft Transfer Paper Wooden Stamps Christmas Stockings Sale Fabric Craft
Home Textiles
Product
Cushion Covers Cushion Pads Table Napkins Table Runners Table Mats Christmas Stockings
Colour
Natural Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers White Cotton Tableware White Linen Cotton Tableware Coloured Cotton Cushion Covers Coloured Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Natural Cotton Christmas Stockings Natural Jute Christmas Stockings Coloured Cotton Christmas Stockings
Material
Cotton Cushion Covers Cotton Canvas Cushion Covers Cotton Christmas Stockings Jute Christmas Stockings
Tableware Budget Table Napkins Sale Home Textiles
Hygiene Wear
Face Coverings Aprons Laundry Bags Hygiene Wear Storage
Packaging
Drawstring Packaging Bags Paper Packaging
Sale
Sale Tote Bags Sale Drawstring Bags Sale Aprons Sale Tea Towels Sale Home Textiles
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how The Clever Baggers uses and protects any information that you give The Clever Baggers when you use this website.
The Clever Baggers is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how The Clever Baggers uses and protects
any information that you give The Clever Baggers when you use this
website.
The Clever Baggers is committed to ensuring that your privacy is
protected.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how The Clever Baggers uses and protects any information that you give The Clever Baggers when you use this website.
The Clever Baggers is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Why we collect and process personal data
Personal data is collected by The Clever Baggers under the lawful basis of Contract. That is, so that we can provide the goods you order from us, or so that we can answer your enquiry which may lead to an order or other form of contract between The Clever Baggers and yourself.
There are three ways we collect personal data through our website:
Enquiry forms such as 'Get a Quote for Printing', 'Get in Touch', 'Employment Application'. Data collected using these forms is processed by us in order to respond to your enquiry During the process of requesting a quotation or placing an order. We require certain personal data, such as name and contact details, to be able to fulfil your order, including delivering your goods and keeping you informed of progress. Some data will be shared with third parties in order to achieve this. Data collected automatically. Our system will record your IP address when you visit our website or complete any online forms on our website. This is an anti-fraud measure used by the majority of businesses operating online.
What we do with your personal Data
Personal data is held in our order management system databases. Some data is shared with third parties in order for us to complete and deliver your order.
Third parties with whom we share your personal data
Please find listed below the third parties with whom we share personal data for the reasons given above. Each business name links to their privacy policy, which will open in a new tab when clicked.
Couriers:FedEx and DPD Payment processors: SagePay and PayPal Mailing list service provider: MailChimp – please note this is only if you have opted to receive our newsletter. Further information in Marketing section.
Website visits and coordination of cookies
In order to better understand the needs of our customers and visitors to our website, we use web analytics services to gather anonymised information via standard tracking technologies.
These services are provided to us by Google, PayPal and Bing (links are to their privacy policies and will open in a new tab).
We also use cookies to enable functionality of the website such as keeping track of shopping cart contents.
For a full list of cookies required for correct functionality of The Clever Baggers website, please see List of Cookies below.
Marketing
Personal data collected when you sign up to our email newsletter is collected and processed under the lawful basis of Consent. As stated above, our mailing service provider is MailChimp and their privacy policy can be viewed here.
You may withdraw consent for this at any time by unsubscribing from the newsletter.
Right to be forgotten
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) gives you a ‘right to be forgotten’. To request this, please contact us via our Contact us form.
Data Retention
In compliance with the standard for ISO 9001:2015, we retain records for a minimum of 2 years from date of order completion.
In compliance with UK law relating to financial record keeping, we retain information for a minimum of 7 years.
List of Cookies
Cookie Name                                               Cookie Description
eu_cookie_law  Stores the status of whether the EU Cookie legislation notification has been acknowledged.
XSRF-TOKEN  Prevents malicious cross-site request forgeries.
ow  Identifies the user and prevents them from needing to log in on every page or when performing an action on the website which requires them to be authenticated.
_ga  Used to distinguish users.
_gid  Used to distinguish users.
_gat  Used to throttle request rate, to prevent attacks on the website.
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Copyright © 2018 The Clever Baggers Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Registered Office: The Clever Baggers Ltd, 5 Four Crosses Business Park, Llanymynech, Powys, SY22 6ST
Company Number: 05775621. VAT number: 870 0715 40
Copyright © 2018 The Clever Baggers Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Registered Office: The Clever Baggers Ltd, 5 Four Crosses Business Park, Llanymynech, Powys, SY22 6ST
Company Number: 05775621. VAT number: 870 0715 40
Copyright © 2018 The Clever Baggers Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Registered Office: The Clever Baggers Ltd, 5 Four Crosses Business Park, Llanymynech, Powys, SY22 6ST
Company Number: 05775621. VAT number: 870 0715 40
We use cookies to ensure that you receive the best experience possible whilst you use our website
OK
